I feel like I can resonate with
everyone's feelings
I got it!
I'll take this one.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
I made a habit
Yes
Project Rio's Type
Botan It was good
Bye☆
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss
You are
The reason I exist
Kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss
I got a souvenir.
Look at this.
I will introduce it.
It's written here.
Cute.
Next, Hokkaido's hot cheese.
I've never seen this before.
Looks delicious.
Yubari melon langdosa.
Haru, you always say langdosa.
It looks delicious. What does it taste
like?
Melon langdosa.
Jagapokkuru. It tastes like salted
scallop.
Looks delicious.
I've never seen it.
This is also a scallop.
I ate the red one.
There was a blue one.
It's salted scallop.
I will buy this as a souvenir.
I love Jagapokkuru.
This is the American trip for today.
This is Anne Marron.
I've seen this before.
Anne Butter.
Wow, this is also...
This is my dad.
This is Julia's dad.
Anne Marron.
Anne Marron and Anne Butter.
Anne Butter.
I can choose.
Anne Marron is good.
Please subscribe to this channel.
This is delicious.
This mask chain.
I'm going to put it on my hand.
Corn.
It's like a man.
It's scary.
What is that?
It's a different one.
I'm going to put it on my hand.
Good morning!
Ta-da!
Today's hairstyle!
Kiyorin came up with it!
Odan-go!
It's a little unusual hairstyle.
I'll do my best for the rehearsal after
this!
I put on my nails.
Pink.
It's a matcha cider with salt candy.
Thank you for watching!
I want to be alone with you
I want to kiss you on a date in a
lady's dress
I just want to see you smile
Don't say that everyone's heart is
broken
Where are you?
I'm in the way
Thank you
I can't stop crying, crying, crying
Good morning!
We are going to perform in Hokkaido.
Thank you.
Let's do it.
2, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Thank you.
Can we start from the first chorus?
Yes.
dating, get a hold of her
Rona-chan, my share of joy
Just as the two of us
were born
Sounds good!
Also, that part you go Umтуーン
i want you to add
ツヨヨヨヨヨヨヨヨヨヨヨデデデデ return
pain
Thank you very much.
I'm in Hokkaido.
I'm going to be a black-haired girl.
Nice to meet you.
Is it over?
Is the rehearsal over?
I'm a little nervous.
I'm sweating a lot today.
I might sweat again on the actual
stage.
I'm nervous today, too.
Thank you for watching.
I like chocolate and sugar.
Which do you like more, chocolate or
sugar?
I don't know.
I like both.
Me too.
Please subscribe to this channel!
Thank you for watching!
How does it taste?
It's salty and soy sauce flavor.
It's fried chicken.
It looks delicious.
I'll eat it.
I got it.
Thank you for watching.
Look at this!
Isn't it great?
We can consume it in a live.
Awesome!
Let's eat!
This is the standard.
Let's enjoy the standard.
I'm not happy.
Did you find it?
I'm not sure.
What is your favorite food?
I'll eat the cake.
It's been a while since I've been to
Sapporo.
I'm at Sapporo.
Kuromi-chan is here for the first time
today.
I'm going to do my best.
I can only come here once a year.
Thank you for coming to the 7th Heart
Gyutto Tour 2022 at Sanrio Characters, a
super-exciting advertising club!
I'm Kanami of the super hot blue, and
I'm also the red-haired girl.
Before we start, I'd like to ask the
audience to be careful of the line.
It's been about a year since we've had
a live show in Hokkaido!
We were really looking forward to it,
so let's make the best memories
together!
And today, everyone, including the
members' hair, is so cute, so look
forward to it!
See you later!
I'm so happy.
Next, Toka, Tarako, Akito, Yurin, Chan,
Rock'n'Roll!
I'm so happy.
Next GyouZZ
I thought of things that no one else
knew about
I can't help it, so goodbye
The important things are always by my
side
It's overflowing so much that I don't
want it
I read the first page of the booklet
【 translation by ロリコ】
Thank you for your hard work.
It's over.
It's amazing.
If you put it in your closet, you'll be
surprised.
This is a cheesecake.
I'm going to eat it after the concert.
My teacher made a cake set.
I was so happy when I found out that
there was this.
This is a cheese tart.
I love this.
I love cheese tart.
I'm going to eat it.
Look! Can you see it?
It's definitely delicious!
「M Connie's Concert Set amazing
people!」
After the climax which everyone in the
cloud did not expect,
finally the location has finally
arrived!
We want to deliver the excitement of
the next generation to as many people as
possible.
We want to step up to the tour through
this Makuhari Messe.
We want to improve our performance so
that we can live up to this venue.
I'm really looking forward to seeing
the smiles of the young people.
I want to make a lot of memories.
October 22nd is...
Let's go!
Special!
Makuhari!
See you!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I wonder why
When I smile, it's like the world is
shining
I can turn my umbrella and feel relaxed
I can't walk without it
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I'm sure someone is getting wet
somewhere
I wonder if it's cold
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
There's a new scenery in front of me
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll draw a fragment of the future
It will guide me
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember it right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights up after the rain
My heart is like a sunny day, I'm happy
My heart is like a sunny day, I ring
the bell of the rainbow
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights up after the rain
My heart is like a sunny day, I shed
tears
I wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la, la la la la la la la